A Guide to the Virginia Secretary of the Commonwealth correspondence, 1891-1911
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Clerk's Correspondence, 1891-1911., Extent: 2.2 cu. ft.
  - Subseries I. General Correspondence, 1891-1911., Extent: 1.7 cu. ft. (Box 11-12)
    Contains a mixture of personal and official correspondence written to and from J.G. Hankins during his employment in the Office of the Secretary of the Commonwealth. The business-related correspondence is very similar to the Secretary's general correspondence and contains mostly requests for legal information and publications. The personal correspondence includes letters pertaining to Hankins' attempt to become State Librarian, letters to and from family members, information about Masonic events, and invitations to weddings and graduations.
    - A, 1896-1910. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - B, 1895-1903. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - B, 1904-1905. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - B, 1906-1910. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - C, 1896-1903. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - C, 1904-1906. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - C, 1906-1910. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - D, 1896-1910. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - E, 1898-1905. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - E, 1906-1909. (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - F, 1891-1910. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - G, 1897-1904. (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - G, 1905-1910. (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - H, 1897-1901. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - H, 1902-1904. (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - H, 1904. (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - H, 1905-1906. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - H, 1907-1909. (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - I, 1905-1909. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - J, 1898-1911. (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - K, 1894-1906. (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - K, 1907-1910. (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - L, 1897-1903. (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - L, 1904-1908. (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - M, 1891-1903. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - M, 1904-1905. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - M, 1906-1907. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - M, 1908-1911. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - N, 1896-1904. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - N, 1905-1910. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - O, 1897-1910. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - P, 1894-1903. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - P, 1904-1910. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - R, 1894-1905. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - R, 1906-1910. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - S, 1895-1903. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - S, 1904-1905. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - S, 1905-1906. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - S, 1907. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - S, 1908-1911. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - T, 1897-1904. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - T, 1905-1910. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - U, 1904-1910. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - V, 1896-1910. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - W, 1896-1903. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - W, 1904. (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - W, 1906-1907. (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - W, 1908-1909. (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Y-Z, 1901-1910. (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1900-1906; undated. (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Subseries II. Subject Correspondence, 1898-1907., Extent: .5 cu. ft. (Box 12-13.)
    Contains letters to and from clerk J.G. Hankins that were grouped according to common topics such as Hankins' unsuccessful campaign to become Secretary of the Commonwealth in 1901, his candidacy for office in 1909, and various receipts.
    Arranged alphabetically by topic.
    - Campaign, A-B, 1901. (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Campaign, C, 1901. (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Campaign, D-F, 1901. (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Campaign, G, 1901. (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Campaign, H, 1901. (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Campaign, I-K, 1901. (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Campaign, L, 1901. (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Campaign, M, 1901. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Campagin, N-R, 1901. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Campaign, S, 1901. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Campaign, T-V, 1901. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Campaign, W-Y, 1901. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Candidacy for Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1909. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Receipts, 1898-1907. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Receipts, 1898-1907. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Receipts, 1898-1907. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Receipts, 1898-1907. (Box 13, Folder 10)